<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Chifra Command Line on</title><link>/docs/chifra/</link><description>Recent content in Chifra Command Line on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/docs/chifra/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Accounts</title><link>/docs/chifra/accounts/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 13:17:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/chifra/accounts/</guid><description>This group of commands is at the heart of TrueBlocks. They allow you to produce and analyze transactional histories for a given Ethereum address.
You may also name addresses; grab the ABI file for a given address; add, delete, and remove monitors, and, most importantly, export transactional histories to various formats, This includes re-directing output to remote or local databases.
chifra list chifra list takes one or more addresses, queries the index of appearances, and builds TrueBlocks monitors.</description></item><item><title>Chain data</title><link>/docs/chifra/chaindata/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 13:17:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/chifra/chaindata/</guid><description>The TrueBlocks tools extract raw blockchain data directly from the node. You may extract block data, transactional data, receipts, logs, and traces. Each tool has it own set of options, allowing you to get exactly the data that you want.
chifra blocks The chifra blocks tool retrieves block data from your Ethereum node or, if previously cached, from the TrueBlocks cache. You may specify multiple blocks per invocation.
By default, chifra blocks queries the full transactional details of the block (including receipts).</description></item><item><title>Chain state</title><link>/docs/chifra/chainstate/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 13:17:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/chifra/chainstate/</guid><description>The two tools in this group deal with the Chain State. As chain state data concerns balances and byte code. it is distinct from Chain Data, which concerns things like blocks, transactions, or traces.
The two tools are chifra state and chifra tokens. The first allows you to query account balances, the byte code of a smart contract (if available), the nonce, and other information about an address. The second tool, chifra tokens, deals with ERC20 and ERC721 token balances and other data.</description></item><item><title>Admin</title><link>/docs/chifra/admin/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 13:17:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/chifra/admin/</guid><description>The Admin component allows you to query the status of the TrueBlocks system. You can query the status; query for information about TrueBlocks caches; control the creation, sharing, and pinning of the TrueBlocks index of appearances; and even serve the data through an API.
See the API documentation for all information about using the API.
chifra config The chifra config program allows you to manage the various TrueBlocks caches. You may list all of the caches, some of the cache, or even individual caches either in terse or full detail.</description></item><item><title>Other</title><link>/docs/chifra/other/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 00:08:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/chifra/other/</guid><description>These commands call some useful miscellaneous tools:
chifra explore a quick way to open a blockchain explorer, ethslurp an older tool that lets you call data from EtherScan. (This has issues of centralization and data quality, see explanation in its section). Note: some of these tools, like ethslurp, require an EtherScan key. Follow these instructions to add a key to your config.
chifra explore chifra explore opens Etherscan (and other explorers &amp;ndash; including our own) to the block identifier, transaction identifier, or address you specify.</description></item><item><title>Configurations</title><link>/docs/chifra/configs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 19:18:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/chifra/configs/</guid><description>Many of the chifra commands allow you to customize their behaviour through configuration files and/or environment variables. These options are documented here.
Environment Variables Each command-line option may be overridden by exporting an environment variable in your shell prior to running a chifra command.
The name of those environment variables is as follows:
The environment variable is ALL_UPPER_CASE The environment variable name preserves underbars in the item_name The name of the variable starts with the group the item belongs to For example: GROUP_ITEM_NAME.</description></item></channel></rss>