<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blog on</title><link>/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blog on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>User contribution: Simple Blockchain Indexing with TrueBlocks</title><link>/blog/user-contribution-simple-blockchain-indexing-with-trueblocks/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 18:10:28 -0400</pubDate><guid>/blog/user-contribution-simple-blockchain-indexing-with-trueblocks/</guid><description>This is a great (and favorable) article about TrueBlocks and how our indexers work written by one of our community members.
Here&amp;rsquo;s the link. Enjoy.</description></item><item><title>FAQ</title><link>/blog/faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 00:45:28 -0400</pubDate><guid>/blog/faq/</guid><description>A few of your more frequently asked questions
Error message: current file does not sequentially follow previous file When using chifra scrape indexer you may get the above message. What this means is a completely empty block was returned from the RPC. When I say completely empty, this means there&amp;rsquo;s not even a miner address. Our scraper thinks that every block must contain at least one address, but on some chains this is not true (for example, on some private chains).</description></item><item><title>forEveryChain</title><link>/blog/foreverychain/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 10:45:28 -0400</pubDate><guid>/blog/foreverychain/</guid><description>Have you ever had the desire to look at every trace of every transaction of every block on every blockchain? Yes? Well, pull up a chair and visit with us for a while.
It’s a Multi-Chain World I’m sure many of you are aware of the coming &amp;ldquo;multi-chain&amp;rdquo; universe of blockchains. You know the one. The one where all sorts of little baby communities of people are going to be doing all sorts of little baby community-like things.</description></item><item><title>Installing Erigon and TrueBlocks as Services on Ubuntu</title><link>/blog/installing-erigon-and-trueblocks-as-services-on-ubuntu/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 18:10:28 -0400</pubDate><guid>/blog/installing-erigon-and-trueblocks-as-services-on-ubuntu/</guid><description>One of our users (Magnus Hansson) has written an excellent article on how to install all three of Erigon, Erigon&amp;rsquo;s RPC, and TrueBlocks as serives on Ubuntu.
How to set up Erigon, Erigon’s RPC and TrueBlocks as services
Not only that &amp;ndash; the blog post is visually wonderful as well.
Thanks Magnus. Looking for some amazing data science from this quarter. Cheers.</description></item><item><title>Other articles published in 2021</title><link>/blog/other-articles-published-in-2021/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 18:10:28 -0400</pubDate><guid>/blog/other-articles-published-in-2021/</guid><description>Here&amp;rsquo;s links to a few other articles we published in 2021 on Medium.
The Rent is Too Damn High The Rent is Too Damn High - Part II Adventures in Difficulty Bombing Calling Smart Contracts with chifra state --call Commanding the Line Compacting ERC20 Logs</description></item><item><title>Has EIP-1559 Fulfilled Its Objectives?</title><link>/blog/has-eip-1559-fulfilled-its-objectives/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 18:10:28 -0400</pubDate><guid>/blog/has-eip-1559-fulfilled-its-objectives/</guid><description>Pintail (twitter) wrote an amazing article on EIP-1559 and its effect on the Ethereum gas market. He used TrueBlocks to extract a bunch of his data. We get a nice mention at the end.
Thanks for the kind words, Pintail!</description></item><item><title>User contribution: Trueblocks Plotter</title><link>/blog/user-contribution-trueblocks-plotter/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2021 18:10:28 -0400</pubDate><guid>/blog/user-contribution-trueblocks-plotter/</guid><description>Matt Solomon, over at ScopeLift, used TrueBlocks as a backend to build a cool tool. TrueBlocks plotter lets you visualize and plot Ethereum data in your browser.
Thanks for expanding the TrueBlocks universe!</description></item><item><title>User post: Local Data Extraction</title><link>/blog/user-post-local-data-extraction/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2021 17:55:05 -0400</pubDate><guid>/blog/user-post-local-data-extraction/</guid><description>Go read the post. Thanks for the support and shoutout!</description></item><item><title>Recipe: Running Against Multiple Rpc Endpoints</title><link>/blog/recipe-running-against-multiple-rpc-endpoints/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 17:13:04 -0400</pubDate><guid>/blog/recipe-running-against-multiple-rpc-endpoints/</guid><description>One user asked if it was possible to run TrueBlocks against multiple RPC endpoints at the same time. This is short recipe to accomplish just that.
Preliminaries The first thing to understand is that the TrueBlocks core runs against a local configuration file stored in your $HOME folder called $HOME/.local/share/TrueBlocks/trueBlocks.toml. It&amp;rsquo;s an almost ridiculously simple file.
The file gets created and populated with default values the first time you build TrueBlocks.</description></item><item><title>Recipe: Getting Erc20 Transfer Events</title><link>/blog/recipe-getting-erc20-transfer-events/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 08:00:02 -0400</pubDate><guid>/blog/recipe-getting-erc20-transfer-events/</guid><description>A TrueBlocks recipe to show every ERC20 Transfer event from a given smart contract.
Note: The following assumes you have a copy of (either by having built it yourself or downloaded it) the TrueBlocks Appearance Index. These instructions also assume that the address you&amp;rsquo;re querying is an ERC 20 smart contract.
Preliminaries To get started, we want to extract (from the TrueBlocks index) a list of every transaction that our address has ever appeared in.</description></item></channel></rss>