<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Problem Statement on</title><link>/docs/</link><description>Recent content in Problem Statement on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Dashboard</title><link>/docs/explorer/dashboard/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 13:56:33 -0500</pubDate><guid>/docs/explorer/dashboard/</guid><description>Monitors Text about Monitors
Details Text about Details
Charts Text about Charts
History Text about History
Event Text about History-Events
Function Text about History-Functions
Reconciliations Text about History-Reconciliations
Custom Text about Custom
Events Text about Events
Functions Text about Functions
Gas Text about Gas
Neighbors Text about Neighbors
Collections Text about Collections</description></item><item><title>Names</title><link>/docs/explorer/names/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 13:56:33 -0500</pubDate><guid>/docs/explorer/names/</guid><description>Named Addresses Text about Named Addresses
Address Tags Text about Address Tags
Signatures Text about Signatures
Named Blocks Text about Named Blocks</description></item><item><title>Explore</title><link>/docs/explorer/explorer/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 13:56:33 -0500</pubDate><guid>/docs/explorer/explorer/</guid><description>Blocks Text about Blocks
Transactions Text about Transactions
Receipts Text about Receipts
Logs Text about Logs
Traces Text about Traces</description></item><item><title>Settings</title><link>/docs/explorer/settings/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 13:56:33 -0500</pubDate><guid>/docs/explorer/settings/</guid><description>Scrapers Text about Scrapers
Indexes Text about Indexes
Caches Text about Caches
Skins Text about Skins
Data Model Text about Data Model</description></item><item><title>Support</title><link>/docs/explorer/support/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 13:56:33 -0500</pubDate><guid>/docs/explorer/support/</guid><description>Contact Us Text about Contact Us
Documentation Text about Documentation
Hot Keys Text about Hot Keys
Licensing Text about Licensing
About Us Text about About Us</description></item><item><title>Install TrueBlocks core</title><link>/docs/install/install-trueblocks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 13:59:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>/docs/install/install-trueblocks/</guid><description>These instructions assume you can navigate the command line and edit configuration files. If you need help with a particular step, see the installation&amp;rsquo;s troubleshooting section.
Quick Install Update GoLang installation go version If your version is less than 1.16, install Go Check other build dependancies or install
☑ Install the other dependencies Clone the repo and compile from the codebase.
While TrueBlocks is still alpha, use the develop branch (we hope to release beta by January, 2022).</description></item><item><title>Build Unchained Index</title><link>/docs/install/get-the-index/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2021 10:19:51 -0300</pubDate><guid>/docs/install/get-the-index/</guid><description>If you want to&amp;hellip; and you don&amp;rsquo;t mind&amp;hellip; then use&amp;hellip; minimize the size of the data stored locally and you want to get started faster&amp;hellip; slower first-time queries on new addresses, an index that&amp;rsquo;s slightly behind the head of the chain, an index created by someone else&amp;hellip; chifra init maximize the speed of first-time queries for new addresses&amp;hellip; longer initial setup time, ~70 GB of local storage, an index that&amp;rsquo;s slightly behind the head of the chain, an index created by someone else&amp;hellip; chifra init --all have a fully-local index, built directly from your own node, that stays up with the chain and maximizes the speed of your queries&amp;hellip; two to three days setup time and running your own local node (such as dAppnode)&amp;hellip;.</description></item><item><title>Install TrueBlocks explorer</title><link>/docs/install/install-explorer/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 08:01:07 -0300</pubDate><guid>/docs/install/install-explorer/</guid><description>First, make sure that you have the chifra-core backend up and running, then run the application from a clone of the explorer repo.
Before you begin ☑ Set up the trueblocks backend using the chifra installation instructions
☑ In a terminal window, run the command chifra serve
Install Keep the chifra serve process running.
Then, in a new terminal, run these commands:
git clone git@github.com:TrueBlocks/trueblocks-explorer.git cd trueblocks-explorer cp .env.example .env yarn yarn develop Open your browser, and access the app from localhost:1234.</description></item><item><title>Introducing chifra</title><link>/docs/using/introducing-chifra/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 13:59:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>/docs/using/introducing-chifra/</guid><description>Similar to git, TrueBlocks has an overarching command called chifra that gives you access to all of the other subcommands.
Type:
chifra You will see a long list of commands similar to this
Usage: chifra command Purpose: Access to all TrueBlocks tools (chifra &amp;lt;cmd&amp;gt; --help for more). Where: Accounts: list list every appearance of an address anywhere on the chain export export full detail of transactions for one or more addresses monitors add, remove, clean, and list address monitors names query addresses or names of well known accounts abis fetches the ABI for a smart contract Chain Data: blocks retrieve one or more blocks from the chain or local cache transactions retrieve one or more transactions from the chain or local cache receipts retrieve receipts for the given transaction(s) logs retrieve logs for the given transaction(s) traces retrieve traces for the given transaction(s) when find block(s) based on date, blockNum, timestamp, or 'special' Chain State: state retrieve account balance(s) for one or more addresses at given block(s) tokens retrieve token balance(s) for one or more addresses at given block(s) Admin: config report on and edit the configuration of the TrueBlocks system daemon initalize and control long-running processes such as the API and the scrapers scrape scan the chain and update the TrueBlocks index of appearances chunks manage, investigate, and display the Unchained Index init initialize the TrueBlocks system by downloading from IPFS Other: explore open a local or remote explorer for one or more addresses, blocks, or transactions slurp fetch data from EtherScan for any address You may get more help on any command by typing chifra &amp;lt;cmd&amp;gt; --help.</description></item><item><title>Some chifra examples</title><link>/docs/using/using-chifra/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 13:59:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>/docs/using/using-chifra/</guid><description>A few more examples in more detail.
Getting Help Every chifra sub-command comes with an associated help page. To get help for chifra itself, simply type
chifra A long list of commands should show. (If you have trouble, see the Installation page.)
To get help for a specific command, type
chifra &amp;lt;cmd&amp;gt; --help To get more detailed help, type
chifra &amp;lt;cmd&amp;gt; --help --verbose 2 Getting System Status The chifra command gives you access to all of TrueBlocks&amp;rsquo; functionality.</description></item></channel></rss>